Before we start doing hands-on in the next section, in this section we're going to look at
some of the basic concepts related to Amazon Bedrock Agent Core and Architecture.
Let's first try and understand what is Amazon Bedrock Agent Core and what is the problem it's
trying to solve. One of the biggest challenges that the enterprise face right now related to the
agentic AI is how do you move the agentic AI applications from the POC face to production ready
business solutions and that's the problem Bedrock Agent Core is trying to solve.
Now how does Amazon Bedrock Agent Core service solve this problem by providing you a set of
capabilities that can help you transition from POC built on agentic AI to production ready
systems. Now let's go ahead and understand in more detail what are these capabilities.
Now rather than explaining the capabilities of the Bedrock Agent Core directly let me explain it
through an enterprise business scenario so that it's more contextual. Now let's say here is our
business use case there's a dream vacation planner travel agency and it wants to build and test an
agentic AI app on their website where the dream vacation planner users can go to their website
and then get an itinerary for their dream destination. Now based on my experience building more
than a dozen applications last couple of years on generative and agentic AI let me just show you
how this scenario would typically work in an enterprise. So you will go to your IT team and maybe
have an application developer who will start building this application through one of the ideas let's
say in this case visual studio code and this is the same application we're going to build later.
Now this application developer is going to start building the application and maybe he will use
one of the open source frameworks, maybe crew AI, Lang chain, Lang graph or AWS trials and in this
case let's assume our application developer uses crew AI framework and then he builds a couple of
agents, maybe a travel research agent which will go and research the internet based on the dream
destination provider let's say London so it will go and search the internet using this tool
separate out give the output back to the travel research agent which will pass it on the summarizer
agent which summarizes all the content and just gives a final output which are the key places to
visit in London what are the cuisines available historical places to visit and so on. Now once his
application is built he will run it on the local host maybe using a streamlit UI he will show a demo
to the business user and business user let's say says hey plan a itinerary for London trip
and it goes through this agenda game application and he gets an itinerary. So just to show you this
is a clear application that we are going to build and let's assume you are the developer so you've
written this code then you have hosted this application in streamlet in your browser then you just
go and show the demo of your POC so you just provided your dream destination and it gives your
dream vacation plan. Now let's go and assume that the business louder application and they want
to move to production where hundreds and thousands of users are going to access this application.
Now in the next lecture we're going to explore how different capabilities of the bedrock agent core
can help this agentic AI application proof of concept to production. Okay so that's pretty much it
from this lecture I'll see you in the next lecture. Thank you.